ACTWU Collective Bargaining Agreements 5619/001
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Philadelphia Joint Board, Coat Fronts & Canvas Pads, 1941-1956 (Box 168, Folder 16)
- Cincinnati Joint Board, Shoulder Pads, 1937-1957 (Box 168, Folder 17)
- Cleveland Joint Board, Coat Fronts, 1941-1952 (Box 168, Folder 18)
- Chicago Joint Board, Coat Fronts, 1941-1957 (Box 169, Folder 1)
- Los Angeles Joint Board, Coat Fronts, 1947-1951 (Box 169, Folder 2)
- Rhode Island, Textron, Inc., 1947-1950 (Box 169, Folder 3)
- Massachusetts, Misc., 1939-1954 (Box 169, Folder 4)
- Connecticut, Park Sportswear Co., Inc., 1953 (Box 169, Folder 5)
- Central States Joint Board, Local #751 and Atlantic Mills Servicing Corp. of Trenton, 1958 (Box 169, Folder 6)
- New York Joint Board, Canvas Fronts & Shoulder Pads, 1947-1950 (Box 169, Folder 7)
- Philadelphia Joint Board, Misc. A-P, 1945-1956 (Box 169, Folder 8)
- Philadelphia Joint Board, Misc. S-Z, 1946-1953 (Box 169, Folder 9)
- Baltimore Joint Board and Jesse Leavey & Co., 1956 (Box 169, Folder 10)
- Illinois, Misc., 1940-1951 (Box 169, Folder 11)
- Indiana, Misc., 1942-1953 (Box 169, Folder 12)
  Boonville Manufacturing Co., Goodyear Engineering Corp., Warren Featherbone Co.
- Missouri, Misc., 1937-1949 (Box 169, Folder 13)
- Michigan, Misc., 1940-1949 (Box 169, Folder 14)
- Ohio, Local #346, Misc., 1938 (Box 169, Folder 15)
- Chicago Joint Board, Misc., 1940-1957 (Box 169, Folder 16)
- Milwaukee Joint Board, Misc., 1937-1960 (Box 169, Folder 17)
- Minnesota Joint Board, Misc., 1941-1957 (Box 169, Folder 18)
- Los Angeles Joint Board, Misc., 1944-1956 (Box 169, Folder 19)
- Scranton & Wilkes-Barre District Joint Board and Brook Manufacturing Co., Inc., 1946-1982 (Box 170, Folder 1)
- New York Joint Board and Brookfield Clothes, Inc., 1977-1980 (Box 170, Folder 2)
- Southern Organizational Department and Brooks Knit Industries, Inc., 1971-1976 (Box 170, Folder 3)
- Pittsburgh District Joint Board and Brookevale Manufacturing Co., Inc., 1972-1984 (Box 170, Folder 4)
- Philadelphia Joint Board and Bodner Neckwear Co., 1958-1973 (Box 170, Folder 5)
- Pittsburgh, Scranton & Wilkes-Barre, West Virginia Regional Joint Board and Bona Sportswear, Inc., 1979-1982 (Box 170, Folder 6)
- New York Joint Board and Bonita Leather Fashions, Inc., 1966-1979 (Box 170, Folder 7)
- Philadelphia Joint Board and Borco Garment Corp., 1969 (Box 170, Folder 8)
- Glove Cities Area Joint Board and Boyce-Lazarus Co., Inc., 1972 (Box 170, Folder 9)
- Minnesota Joint Board and Brainerd Garment Co., 1968-1980 (Box 170, Folder 10)
- Midwest Regional Joint Board and Brigham Apparel Corp., 1967-1976 (Box 170, Folder 11)
- New York Joint Board, Local #377 and Bristol Clothing Manufacturing, Inc., 1977-1980 (Box 170, Folder 12)
- Amalgamated Service and Allied Industries and Blue Point Laundry, 1975 (Box 170, Folder 13)
- Joint Board of Shirt, Leisurewear, Robe, Glove and Rainwear Workers' Union and Blassport, Ltd., 1975-1983 (Box 170, Folder 14)
- Pittsburgh District Joint Board and Blairsville Manufacturing Co., Inc., 1978-1981 (Box 170, Folder 15)
- New York Joint Board and Birbaum Bros., 1966-1979 (Box 170, Folder 16)
- Massachusetts, Local #377 and Bedford Shirtmakers Corp., 1969 (Box 170, Folder 17)
- Boston Joint Board and Best Coat Co., 1954-1979 (Box 170, Folder 18)
- Pittsburgh District Joint Board and Big River Manufacturing Co., 1979-1982 (Box 170, Folder 19)
- Pittsburgh, Scranton & Wilkes-Barre, West Virginia Regional Joint Board and Bee & Gee Pants Co., Inc., 1979 (Box 170, Folder 20)
- New England, Local #452 and Belfast Manufacturing Co., 1943-1969 (Box 170, Folder 21)
- Chicago Joint Board and Bell Pants Co., 1963-1971 (Box 170, Folder 22)
- Local #126 and Bender Brothers Sportswear, Inc., 1956-1982 (Box 170, Folder 23)
- Lehigh Valley Joint Board and Bangor Clothing Co. Coat Shop, 1968 (Box 170, Folder 24)
- Philadelphia Joint Board and Bannercraft Clothing Co., Inc., 1962-1965 (Box 170, Folder 25)
- Southern California Joint Board and Banning Shirt Corp., 1965-1968 (Box 170, Folder 26)
- Joint Board of Shirt, Leisurewear, Robe, Glove and Rainwear Workers' Union and Thomas J. Barile Co., Inc., 1975-1982 (Box 170, Folder 27)
- Southern California Joint Board and Bassi - California, Inc., 1966 (Box 170, Folder 28)
- New York Joint Board and Baxter Clothes, Inc., 1977-1980 (Box 170, Folder 29)
- Connecticut, Local #125 and Bay Products, Inc., 1961-1966 (Box 170, Folder 30)
- Joint Board of Shirt, Leisurewear, Robe, Glove and Rainwear Workers' Union and Bayard International, Inc., 1984 (Box 170, Folder 31)
- Cincinnati Joint Board and Beau Brummel Ties, Inc., 1969-1979 (Box 170, Folder 32)
- New York Joint Board and B.M.D. Leather Co., Inc., 1980 (Box 170, Folder 33)
- Glove Cities Area Joint Board and C.J. Bachner, 1961-1976 (Box 170, Folder 34)
- Eastern Pennsylvania Joint Board and Bally Pants Co., 1963-1976 (Box 170, Folder 35)
- Baltimore Regional Joint Board and Baltimore Sportswear, Inc., 1969-1976 (Box 170, Folder 36)
- Philadelphia Joint Board and B.J. Clothing Co., Inc., 1966-1982 (Box 170, Folder 37)
- Joint Board of Shirt, Leisurewear, Robe, Glove and Rainwear Workers' Union and Atlantic Shirt Co., Inc., 1975-1982 (Box 170, Folder 38)
- Amalgamated Service and Allied Industries and Atlantic Towel Service, 1975 (Box 170, Folder 39)
- New York Joint Board and Ambassador Clothes, Inc., 1977-1982 (Box 170, Folder 40)
- Glove Cities Area Joint Board and Ambroson Gloves, Inc., 1972-1976 (Box 170, Folder 41)
- New York Joint Board and American Coat Front Co., 1968-1977 (Box 170, Folder 42)
- Pennsylvania Joint Board and Amil Manufacturing Co., Inc., 1976-1979 (Box 171, Folder 1)
- Joint Board of Shirt, Leisurewear, Robe, Glove and Rainwear Workers' Union and Andlee Sportswear Corp., 1975-1982 (Box 171, Folder 2)
- Pennsylvania Joint Board and Anthracite Apparel, Inc., 1975-1980 (Box 171, Folder 3)
- New York Joint Board and Mark Anthony Pants, Ltd., 1980 (Box 171, Folder 4)
- Chicago Joint Board and Apco Manufacturing Co., Inc., 1969-1976 (Box 171, Folder 5)
- Joint Board of Shirt, Leisurewear, Robe, Glove and Rainwear Workers' Union and Apex Sportswear, Inc., 1973-1975 (Box 171, Folder 6)
- Joint Board of Shirt, Leisurewear, Robe, Glove and Rainwear Workers' Union and Apex Die Cutting Corp., 1972-1979 (Box 171, Folder 7)
- Philadelphia Joint Board and Apollo Clothes, 1980 (Box 171, Folder 8)
- Philadelphia Joint Board and Apprendi, Inc., 1977-1980 (Box 171, Folder 9)
- New York Joint Board and Arielle Leather Fashions, Inc., 1977-1982 (Box 171, Folder 10)
- Massachusetts, Local #177 and Arkay Pants Co., 1955-1976 (Box 171, Folder 11)
- New York Joint Board and Arrow Clothes, Inc., 1982 (Box 171, Folder 12)
- Philadelphia Joint Board and Arrorwhead Sportswear, 1958-1974 (Box 171, Folder 13)
- Amalgamated Service and Allied Industries and Artistic Laundry, Inc., 1975 (Box 171, Folder 14)
- Joint Board of Shirt, Leisurewear, Robe, Glove and Rainwear Workers' Union and Associated Glove Crafters, Inc., 1966-1969 (Box 171, Folder 15)
- Lehigh Valley Joint Board and Astro Apparel, Inc., 1979 (Box 171, Folder 16)
- Pennsylvania Joint Board and William Atkin Co., Inc., 1976-1979 (Box 171, Folder 17)
- New York Joint Board and Acme Leathers & Sportswear, Inc., 1966-1979 (Box 171, Folder 18)
- Southwest Regional Joint Board and Admiral Sportswear, Inc., 1969-1972 (Box 171, Folder 19)
- Amalgamated Service and Allied Industries and Affiliated Laundries, Inc., 1975 (Box 171, Folder 20)
- Southern California Joint Board and Alan John of California, Inc., 1978-1980 (Box 171, Folder 21)
- Southern California Joint Board and Alexander Shirt (Palomar Shirt), 1975-1976 (Box 171, Folder 22)
- Puerto Rico Joint Board and Alisa Sportswear, Inc., 1969 (Box 171, Folder 23)
- New York Joint Board and Allstyles Sportswear, Inc., 1978-1979 (Box 171, Folder 24)
- Chicago Joint Board and Ace Leathers Products, Inc., 1966 (Box 171, Folder 25)
- New York Joint Board and A.M.L. Leather Fashions, Inc., 1981-1982 (Box 171, Folder 26)
- New York Joint Board and A & H, Inc., 1970-1982 (Box 171, Folder 27)
- New York Joint Board and A & F Originals, Inc., 1974-1982 (Box 171, Folder 28)
- Southwest Regional Joint Board and A & A Manufacturing Corp., 1970-1972 (Box 171, Folder 29)
- Cleveland Joint Board and Buckeye Pants, 1974 (Box 171, Folder 30)
- Joint Board of Shirt, Leisurewear, Robe, Glove and Rainwear Workers' Union and Byrnes-Lewis, Ltd., 1975-1982 (Box 171, Folder 31)
- Boston Joint Board and Byron Clothing Manufacturing Co., Inc., 1977 (Box 171, Folder 32)
- Southwest Regional Joint Board and Cal-Crest Outerwear, Inc., 1969-1972 (Box 171, Folder 33)
- Southern California Joint Board and Cal Made Manufacturing Co., 1966-1979 (Box 171, Folder 34)
- Pittsburgh, Scranton & Wilkes-Barre, West Virginia Regional Joint Board and Campo Slacks, Inc., 1975-1976 (Box 171, Folder 35)
- Cleveland Joint Board and Cannon Tailoring Co., 1977 (Box 171, Folder 36)
- Puerto Rico Joint Board and Caribannin, Inc., 1965 (Box 171, Folder 37)
- Puerto Rico Joint Board and Caribe Sports Co., 1961-1966 (Box 172, Folder 1)
- Baltimore Regional Joint Board and Carlo's Pants Co., 1972-1977 (Box 172, Folder 2)
- Joint Board of Shirt, Leisurewear, Robe, Glove and Rainwear Workers' Union and Carmen Sportswear, 1975-1979 (Box 172, Folder 3)
- Southern California Joint Board and Victor Carnevali, 1977 (Box 172, Folder 4)
- South Jersey Joint Board and Carousel Slack Co., 1977-1982 (Box 172, Folder 5)
- Tannery and Leather Workers Union, Local #1712 and Cayadutta Tanning Co., Inc., 1972-1974 (Box 172, Folder 6)
- Amalgamated Service and Allied Industries and Cervantes Laundry, Inc., 1975 (Box 172, Folder 7)
- West Central Tennessee Joint Board and Chester County Sportswear Co., Inc., 1984 (Box 172, Folder 8)
- Local #158 and Chief Apparel, Inc., 1968-1974 (Box 172, Folder 9)
- Philadelphia Joint Board and Chief Apparel, Inc., 1955-1976 (Box 172, Folder 10)
- New York Joint Board and Tino Chillemi, Inc., 1977-1982 (Box 172, Folder 11)
- Philadelphia Joint Board and Chips 'n Twigs, Inc., 1977-1982 (Box 172, Folder 12)
- Boston Joint Board and Clift Manufacturing Co., Inc., 1955-1979 (Box 172, Folder 13)
- New York Joint Board and Clifton Clothing Co. (Pat and Everett Vallorano), 1982 (Box 172, Folder 14)
- Philadelphia Joint Board and Samuel Coane, Inc., 1969-1979 (Box 172, Folder 15)
- South Jersey Joint Board and Coat Corp. of N.J., 1974-1982 (Box 172, Folder 16)
- New York Joint Board and Isaac Cohen Clothing Corp., 1977-1980 (Box 172, Folder 17)
- Minnesota Joint Board and Cohn-Feldman Co., 1970-1976 (Box 172, Folder 18)
- Philadelphia Joint Board and John Colletti, Inc., 1964-1976 (Box 172, Folder 19)
- Southwest Regional Joint Board and Community Towel and Uniform Co., 1974-1986 (Box 172, Folder 20)
- Montreal Joint Board and Confections Jayet, Inc., 1981-1989 (Box 172, Folder 21)
- Pittsburgh District Joint Board and Connellsville Sportswear Co., 1969-1979 (Box 172, Folder 22)
- Joint Board of Shirt, Leisurewear, Robe, Glove and Rainwear Workers' Union and Connie Sportswear, Inc., 1975-1982 (Box 172, Folder 23)
- Joint Board of Shirt, Leisurewear, Robe, Glove and Rainwear Workers' Union and Copiague Knitwear Corp., 1975-1976 (Box 172, Folder 24)
- Philadelphia Joint Board and Corama Fashions, Ltd., 1977-1980 (Box 172, Folder 25)
- Joint Board of Shirt, Leisurewear, Robe, Glove and Rainwear Workers' Union and Corona Shirt Co., 1975-1982 (Box 172, Folder 26)
- New York Joint Board and Courageous Clothes, Ltd., 1977-1982 (Box 172, Folder 27)
- Joint Board of Shirt, Leisurewear, Robe, Glove and Rainwear Workers' Union and Miriam Couture's, Ltd., 1983 (Box 172, Folder 28)
- Buffalo Joint Board and Cresbury Clothes, Inc., 1971 (Box 172, Folder 29)
- Lehigh Valley Joint Board and Cross Country, Egypt, Coats, 1974 (Box 172, Folder 30)
- Lehigh Valley Joint Board and Cross Country, Egypt, Pants, 1974-1975 (Box 172, Folder 31)
- Philadelphia Joint Board and Cross Country Clothes, 1977-1980 (Box 172, Folder 32)
- Winnipeg Joint Council, Local #459 and Crown Cap Manufacturing Co., Ltd., 1983-1985 (Box 172, Folder 33)
- Tannery and Leather Workers Union, Local #1712 and Crown Leather Finishing, Inc., 1972-1974 (Box 172, Folder 34)
- South Jersey Joint Board and Crown Pants Co., 1977 (Box 172, Folder 35)
- Montreal Joint Board and Croydon Manufacturing Co., Ltd, 1971-1987 (Box 172, Folder 36)
- Local #340A and Cuckoo Clock Manufacturing Co., Inc., 1970 (Box 173, Folder 1)
- Kentuckiana Joint Board and Cumberland Manufacturing Co., Inc., 1966-1982 (Box 173, Folder 2)
- Amalgamated Service and Allied Industries and Custom Art Laundry & Valet Service, Inc., 1975 (Box 173, Folder 3)
- Eastern Shore Joint Board and D & F Shirt Co., Inc., 1976-1982 (Box 173, Folder 4)
- New England, Local #125 and D & I Shirt Co. (Danfra), 1958-1985 (Box 173, Folder 5)
- Joint Board of Shirt, Leisurewear, Robe, Glove and Rainwear Workers' Union and D & W Robes, 1975-1979 (Box 173, Folder 6)
- Joint Board of Shirt, Leisurewear, Robe, Glove and Rainwear Workers' Union and Damon Creations, Inc., 1966-1987 (Box 173, Folder 7)
- Joint Board of Shirt, Leisurewear, Robe, Glove and Rainwear Workers' Union and Dan Nico Sportswear, Inc., 1980 (Box 173, Folder 8)
- Joint Board of Shirt, Leisurewear, Robe, Glove and Rainwear Workers' Union and Dar-Jo Manufacturing Co., 1972-1982 (Box 173, Folder 9)
- Massachusetts, Local #177 and Darwood Manufacturing Co., 1959-1980 (Box 173, Folder 10)
- Chicago Joint Board and Davenshire, Inc., 1961-1976 (Box 173, Folder 11)
- New York Joint Board and De Hota Cutting, Inc., 1979-1983 (Box 173, Folder 12)
- Philadelphia Joint Board and De Luca Sportswear Co., 1977-1982 (Box 173, Folder 13)
- New York Joint Board and Dean Clothing Co., Inc., 1977 (Box 173, Folder 14)
- Baltimore Regional Joint Board and Devon, Inc., 1977-1985 (Box 173, Folder 15)
- New York Joint Board, Local #178 and Dawn Fashions Leather, Ltd., 1974-1979 (Box 173, Folder 16)
- New York Joint Board and Delton, Ltd., 1977-1980 (Box 173, Folder 17)
- New York Joint Board and Dirzis Products Co., Inc., 1977 (Box 173, Folder 18)
- Amalgamated Service and Allied Industries and Douglaston Laundry, 1975 (Box 173, Folder 19)
- Southern California Joint Board and Duke of Hollywood, 1962-1975 (Box 173, Folder 20)
- New York Joint Board and Dunrite Boyswear Co., Inc., 1977-1982 (Box 173, Folder 21)
- Joint Board of Shirt, Leisurewear, Robe, Glove and Rainwear Workers' Union and Durable Sportswear Co., Inc., 1975-1982 (Box 173, Folder 22)
- Pittsburgh District Joint Board and Dust Proof Manufacturing Co., Inc., 1977-1980 (Box 173, Folder 23)
- General Office and Eagle of Alabama, Inc., 1976-1979 (Box 173, Folder 24)
- Eagle Shirtmakers, Inc., 1972-1976 (Box 173, Folder 25)
- Eastern Pennsylvania Joint Board and Easton Clothing Co., 1977-1980 (Box 173, Folder 26)
- Chicago Joint Board and Economical Pants Co., 1963-1977 (Box 173, Folder 27)
- Puerto Rico Joint Board and Erdo Corp. (Anasco Gloves, Inc.), 1967 (Box 173, Folder 28)
- Southwest Regional Joint Board and Ralph Edwards Sportswear, Inc., 1972 (Box 173, Folder 29)
- New York Joint Board and Ehrenberg Clothing Corp., 1977 (Box 173, Folder 30)
- New York Joint Board, Local #178 and Eiffel Leather Fashions, 1968-1979 (Box 173, Folder 31)
- South Jersey Joint Board and Elkton Fashions, 1977 (Box 173, Folder 32)
- Joint Board of Shirt, Leisurewear, Robe, Glove and Rainwear Workers' Union and Famous Cottons, Inc. (Niko Manufacturing), 1975-1979 (Box 174, Folder 1)
- Joint Board of Shirt, Leisurewear, Robe, Glove and Rainwear Workers' Union and Falcon Sportswear, 1977-1982 (Box 174, Folder 2)
- New England Regional Joint Board, Local #177 and Fall River Shirts (Shelburne Shirt Co.), 1959-1982 (Box 174, Folder 3)
- Philadelphia Joint Board and Fashion Items, Inc., 1967-1976 (Box 174, Folder 4)
- Joint Board of Shirt, Leisurewear, Robe, Glove and Rainwear Workers' Union and Fashion Square, Ltd., 1975-1982 (Box 174, Folder 5)
- Joint Board of Shirt, Leisurewear, Robe, Glove and Rainwear Workers' Union and Fatima Sportswear, Inc., 1969-1979 (Box 174, Folder 6)
- New York Joint Board and Fields Sportswear, Inc., 1966-1979 (Box 174, Folder 7)
- Amalgamated Service and Allied Industries and Finest Steam Laundry, Inc., 1975 (Box 174, Folder 8)
- Philadelphia Joint Board and Harry Fischer Corp., 1977-1982 (Box 174, Folder 9)
- Southern Organizational Department and Franklin Apparel Manufacturing Co., 1980 (Box 174, Folder 10)
- Pennsylvania Joint Board and Freeland Manufacturing Co., 1978-1979 (Box 174, Folder 11)
- Pennsylvania Joint Board and Freeland Sportswear Co., 1976-1979 (Box 174, Folder 12)
- Philadelphia Joint Board and Fulton Clothes Co., Inc., 1977-1980 (Box 174, Folder 13)
- Joint Board of Shirt, Leisurewear, Robe, Glove and Rainwear Workers' Union and Flamingo Togs, Inc., 1972-1979 (Box 174, Folder 14)
- New York Joint Board and Benjamin Flax, Inc., 1977 (Box 174, Folder 15)
- Southwest Regional Joint Board and Fordyce Apparel Co., 1972 (Box 174, Folder 16)
- Pennsylvania Joint Board and Morris Fishman Manufacturing Co., Inc., 1976-1982 (Box 174, Folder 17)
- New England Regional Joint Board, Local #125 and Fair Manufacturing Co., Inc., 1954-1982 (Box 174, Folder 18)
- Pennsylvania, Fair-Tex Mills, Inc., 1979-1980 (Box 174, Folder 19)
- West Central Tennessee Joint Board and Forest Hills Sportswear Co., 1959-1976 (Box 174, Folder 20)
- Pennsylvania Joint Board and Fox-Knapp Manufacturing Co., 1979-1982 (Box 174, Folder 21)
- Tannery and Leather Workers' Union, Local #1712 and Framglo Tanners, Inc., 1967-1974 (Box 174, Folder 22)
- New Jersey, Enco Originals, 1978 (Box 174, Folder 23)
- Glove Cities Area Joint Board and R.J. Evans Glove Co., Inc., 1969-1974 (Box 174, Folder 24)
- New England, Local #126 and Fulton Shirt Co., Inc., 1958-1976 (Box 174, Folder 25)
- New York Joint Board and Evette Leather Fashion, Inc., 1966-1979 (Box 174, Folder 26)
- Southwest Regional Joint Board and Excello Shirts, Inc., 1975-1985 (Box 174, Folder 27)
- Pittsburgh District Joint Board and Ellwood Knitting Mills, Inc., 1969-1979 (Box 174, Folder 28)
- Pennsylvania Joint Board and Emenee Manufacturing Corp., 1979 (Box 174, Folder 29)
- Pennsylvania Joint Board and Emmaus Manufacturing Co., 1979-1982 (Box 174, Folder 30)
- Joint Board of Shirt, Leisurewear, Robe, Glove and Rainwear Workers' Union and Empire Shirt Trimming Co., Inc., 1969-1982 (Box 174, Folder 31)
- New York Joint Board of Shirt, Leisurewear, Robe, Glove and Rainwear Workers' Union and G & S Knit Shirts, Inc., 1975-1982 (Box 174, Folder 32)
- Joint Board of Shirt, Leisurewear, Robe, Glove and Rainwear Workers' Union and Gabey Shirt Co., Inc., 1975-1982 (Box 174, Folder 33)
- New York Joint Board and H.M. Gammon Manufacturing Corp., 1978 (Box 174, Folder 34)
- Joint Board of Shirt, Leisurewear, Robe, Glove and Rainwear Workers' Union and Gem Sportswear, Inc., 1969-1976 (Box 174, Folder 35)
- New England Regional Joint Board, Local #1 and #181 and G.T., Inc., 1977-1982 (Box 174, Folder 36)
- Baltimore Regional Joint Board and General Clothing Co., Inc., 1966-1979 (Box 174, Folder 37)
- Midwest Joint Board and Gerry (Outdoor Sports Industries, Inc.), 1975-1981 (Box 175, Folder 1)
- Amalgamated Service and Allied Industries and Gibraltar Industries, Inc., 1971-1977 (Box 175, Folder 2)
- Chicago and Central States Joint Board and Gimbels Midwest, Inc., 1974-1985 (Box 175, Folder 3)
- Chicago and Central States Joint Board and J.A. Gits Plastic Corp., 1983-1986 (Box 175, Folder 4)
- New York Joint Board and B. Glanzrock, Inc., 1977-1982 (Box 175, Folder 5)
- Local #158 and Globe Sport Products Co., 1982 (Box 175, Folder 6)
- Joint Board of Shirt, Leisurewear, Robe, Glove and Rainwear Workers' Union and Glove Technics, 1966-1982 (Box 175, Folder 7)
- Philadelphia Joint Board and Max Golden & Son, Inc., 1977-1980 (Box 175, Folder 8)
- Philadelphia Joint Board and M. Goldenberg & Sons, Inc., 1969-1976 (Box 175, Folder 9)
- New England Regional Joint Board, Local #187 and Edward Goldman Co., 1979 (Box 175, Folder 10)
- Southwest Regional Joint Board and Good Luck Glove Co., 1959-1984 (Box 175, Folder 11)
- New York Joint Board and Gordon & Mallow, Inc., 1977-1982 (Box 175, Folder 12)
- Philadelphia Joint Board and Gordon of Philadelphia, 1980-1985 (Box 175, Folder 13)
- Philadelphia Joint Board and Gordon of Philadelphia, 1977-1982 (Box 175, Folder 14)
- Joint Board of Shirt, Leisurewear, Robe, Glove and Rainwear Workers' Union and Grace Robe Co., 1972-1979 (Box 175, Folder 15)
- Chicago Joint Board and Rubin Grais & Sons, Inc., 1969-1985 (Box 175, Folder 16)
- Joint Board of Shirt, Leisurewear, Robe, Glove and Rainwear Workers' Union and Grand Sportswear, Inc., 1975-1976 (Box 175, Folder 17)
- New York Joint Board and Grand Uniform Co., 1975-1980 (Box 175, Folder 18)
- Amalgamated Service and Allied Industries and Grand View Laundry, 1975 (Box 175, Folder 19)
- Buffalo Joint Board and John Granelli & Son, Inc., 1977 (Box 175, Folder 20)
- New York Joint Board and I. Greenberg, Inc., 1977-1980 (Box 175, Folder 21)
- Pittsburgh District Joint Board and Greenway Manufacturing Co., 1969-1982 (Box 175, Folder 22)
- Joint Board of Shirt, Leisurewear, Robe, Glove and Rainwear Workers' Union and Greystone Shirt Co., Inc., 1975-1979 (Box 175, Folder 23)
- Southwest Regional Joint Board and Grove Co., 1969 (Box 175, Folder 24)
- Joint Board of Shirt, Leisurewear, Robe, Glove and Rainwear Workers' Union and Gwen Sportswear, Inc., 1975-1985 (Box 175, Folder 25)
- New York Joint Board and H & M Neckwear Co., Inc., 1977-1980 (Box 175, Folder 26)
- Southern Organizational Department and Halltex Clothing Co., Inc., 1977-1983 (Box 175, Folder 27)
- Southern Organizational Department and Hansley Enterprises, Inc., 1969-1979 (Box 175, Folder 28)
- New York Joint Board and Harvard Pad Co., Inc., 1968-1977 (Box 175, Folder 29)
- Joint Board of Shirt, Leisurewear, Robe, Glove and Rainwear Workers' Union and Hema Shirt Co., 1975-1979 (Box 175, Folder 30)
- New York Joint Board and Henmur Cut Make & Trim, Inc., 1980 (Box 175, Folder 31)
- Joint Board of Shirt, Leisurewear, Robe, Glove and Rainwear Workers' Union and Hermark Knitwear Corp., 1975-1982 (Box 175, Folder 32)
- Philadelphia Joint Board and Hi-Craft Clothing, Co., 1977-1982 (Box 175, Folder 33)
- Pittsburgh District Joint Board and Kenton Manufacturing Co., 1973-1979 (Box 176, Folder 1)
- Joint Board of Shirt, Leisurewear, Robe, Glove and Rainwear Workers' Union and Kenwood Knitting Mills, 1975-1982 (Box 176, Folder 2)
- New York Joint Board and A. Klein Uniform Co., Inc., 1980-1982 (Box 176, Folder 3)
- Tennessee, Knox Manufacturing Co., 1977-1980 (Box 176, Folder 4)
- Philadelphia Joint Board and Koko Rainwear Corp., 1974 (Box 176, Folder 5)
- Chicago Joint Board, Midwest Joint Board, Milwaukee Joint Board and Krasno Bros. Glove and Mitten Co., Inc., 1938-1983 (Box 176, Folder 6)
- New York Joint Board and L & D Outerwear, Inc., 1976-1979 (Box 176, Folder 7)
- New York Joint Board and L & I Sportswear, 1966-1979 (Box 176, Folder 8)
- Joint Board of Shirt, Leisurewear, Robe, Glove and Rainwear Workers' Union and L & L Shirt Co., Inc., 1975-1982 (Box 176, Folder 9)
- Joint Board of Shirt, Leisurewear, Robe, Glove and Rainwear Workers' Union and La Sport, Inc. (Fran Mar), 1975-1976 (Box 176, Folder 10)
- Amalgamated Service and Allied Industries and Lafayette Select - Public Laundry & Cleaners, 1975 (Box 176, Folder 11)
- Eastern Pennsylvania Joint Board and Lansdale Manufacturing, Inc., 1976 (Box 176, Folder 12)
- New York Joint Board and Lanorda Clothing Contractors, Inc., 1977-1980 (Box 176, Folder 13)
- Pennsylvania Joint Board and Lansford Apparel Co., 1976-1985 (Box 176, Folder 14)
- Chicago and Central States Joint Board and Laser Corp., 1986 (Box 176, Folder 15)